I ate seven pints of ice cream and
sorbet this week and was still able to
maintain a caloric deficit. Here's how I
did it. I used my Ninja Creamy to
recreate my favorite frozen desserts,
but in a much healthier way. Here are
the seven pints I made this week. That
first one that you saw was a double
Oreo. It is my favorite Ninja Creamy
recipe that I've ever made. You guys
have to try it. This next one is a
matcha flavor. It's literally as good as
real matcha ice cream. 145 calories. You
can't beat that. This is a chocolate
fudge brownie flavor recreating the
famous Ben & Jerry's flavor. Phenomenal.
Then we did a little Dubai chocolate
dupe. This was a pistachio base with a
chocolate shell and then some toasted
coconut in there. Really, really good.
If you want me to do a chocolate based
pistachio shell, let me know. I'll try
that out. And then I did a peanut butter
cup. This one is just an absolute
classic. Vanilla base with peanut butter
cups mixed in and on top. Good little
sweet and salty combo. And then I did
some sorbets. Given that it is coming up
on summer, I've just been craving fruit
and this is the perfect refreshing and
healthy snack. It's literally just two
ingredients, whatever fruit you want. I
did grape and watermelon and then Sprite
Zero. Before you ask for these recipes,
they're already all posted on my page.
So check out my page, drop me a follow.
I'm posting new ones every single